have you always been interested in
Insurance products but don't have the
budget for it yet or you feel you're not
ready for the commitment we're here to
help you be ready with the Manulife shop
and it's 365 ready products the Manulife
Shop features three kinds of 365 ready
insurance plans all of which allow you
to get the coverage you need at prices
you can definitely afford just to give
you an example an accident insurance
coverage is available for as low as 199
pesos per year yes per year plus it's as
easy as shopping on your favorite online
shops you simply first go to the
Manulife website choose the plan that
suits your needs read and agree to the
statement and Declaration on the site
upload and submit a valid ID then fill
up the application form pay for your
plan and submit that's it quick easy and
affordable so go to the Manulife website
and start choosing your 365 ready plan
right now